

## **EDUCATION**

# K K Shashtri Commerce College

Batchelor of Commerce, Accountancy 2006-2008

## **SKILLS**

In and out of Iran Exports
MS Office
CRM
SWIFT
Effective Communication
Multitasking
Team work

## CONTACT

- +91-9909901108
- rose.shah1984@gmail.com
- Flat No 1403, Block J,
  Parishkar Phase 2, Khokhra
  Circle, Ahmedabad-380008.

# ROSHANI JOSHI

# **ABOUT ME**

I have worked as an Exports Manager at Treasury Branch, UCO Bank, with four years of experience in this field, I have worked with various exporters, exporting all sort of goods such as tea, pharmaceutical, chemicals, rice, cotton, garments etc. in the country of Iran, wherein I looked after entire exports operations starting from sending swifts to pre and post shipment documents to release of payments post shipments. During my incumbency, I also got my hands on back office work & fund management at Treasury Branch of the said bank. Barring aforementioned assignments, I additionally carry the experience in General banking and Branch operations. In my 9 years of career at UCO Bank, in the recent past, I happened to blow whistles against the corrupt practices being carried at the hands of certain executives of the bank, consequent upon which, I have been removed from the services.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### **UCO BANK**

Exports Manager & Treasury Operations 2016-2019

- Entire Iran Exports Operations at UCO Bank Treasury Branch
- Managed Iranian banks' accounts and oil import payments to the companies called MRPL, Indian Oil Corp. etc.
- Sending of MT103, 707, 940 and other sort of swifts to Iranian and local banks
- Perusal of invoices and packing lists, & release of Advance payments to the accounts of exporters
- Examining the authenticity of companies, perusal of LCs & pre and post shipment documents
- Release of exports payments upon shipment of goods/docs
   Issuance of BRCs
- Management of short and long term money market & capital market instruments
- Fund Management for the maintainance of CRR and SLR

Manager- General Banking Operations 2013 to 2015 & 2019 to 2021

- Entire Branch Operations at various branches of UCO Bank
- Perusal and preparation of loan documents, sanctioning of Loans, Loan and other sorts of Account Openings
- Follow up and recovery of NPA Accounts
- ATM Management, Preparation of quarterly statements
- Customer grievances resolution, RTGS, NEFT, Clearing,
   Drafts, FDRs, Online transactions
- Physical Cash Verification